

Subramanian Natarajan

About Me

I am a highly motivated DevOps Engineer with 1+ years of experience in building, managing, and monitoring cloud-based applications. I am adept at configuring and automating applications, setting up continuous integration, and ensuring maximum performance and reliability of applications.

Contact



+49-163-814-7351



Subramanian.natarajan@ Yahoo.com



Education

IU International University

- Master's in computer Science.
- 2021-2023

Anna University in India

- B.tech Information Technology
- 2008-2011

Language

- English
- Germany (basic)

Certificates

PG in Cloud Computing

- AWS Cloud Services
- Azure Cloud Services

Kubernetes Cerfication

• KodeKloud Online.

Experience

CloudBiz LLC

2020 - 2021

Junior - Full Stack developer

- The project was a full stack web application for a task management system for an internal team.
- Work with Javascript , Vue.js , HTML5, css3, postgreSQL
- Responsibilities: Developed the front end components, wrote unit tests using mocha and enzyme integrated with the back-end deployed the application.
- set up and developed a CI/CD pipeline using tools such as Jenkins and GIT lab.
- Increase database admin effectiveness by 25%

TOBS LLC

2016 - 2020

- Developed industry-specific Tally Software modules
- Maintained application services and implemented various project solutions
- Expertise in software customization (Forms Design, UDF creation, Integration With other Apps, Data Exporting from Tally and Reports.)
- Maintain composure and patience while handling difficult customer situations in order to troubleshoot computer hardware, application, and network infrastructure problems.

Skill & Tools

- Language : Python , Go, Shell Script, HTML/CSS, Yaml.
- Frameworks: Django, React, Vuejs, Firebase.
- Technologies : Docker , Kubernetes, MySql, GitHub
- Terraform, AWS services, Azure DevOps, Bitbucket.